[{"answer": "The subway certainly is wonderful my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes, let's look for treasure", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You want my friend and my friend of that place, I want you to bring me and my friends IN to that place. That sounds like a fair trade doesn't it. Super, let's get started", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hey, relax, guy! Trust m", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I never knew you had a daughter, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, you never did, my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "My God! What a fascinating story, my friend! Especially the part aboot my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Then I will go with you, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "People seem to really like it. I even have a date this Friday", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "that place is dangerous. You guys shouldn't go there", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What do you mean? Why are you calling him 'Ugly Bob'", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " You told me your name was Handsome my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Hey my friend, you helped me get rid of my friend and my friend, and I appreciate that... But why are framed pictures of you going up all over that place", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No I don't need a rest! I want to know what this is all aboot", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hey, relax fella, I'm just making it so that my friend and my friend can never come back to that place again. I just need a couple of things, and then I'm gonna head back to that place", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "that place, that place, what the hell's the difference? Relax, guy", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What are you doing, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Cancer", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend, the U.S. government is becoming worried", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You seem to be... Taking over that place", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Worried? About what? Take a load off. Relax", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Taking over that place? Me? Hey, you need a rest fella. I'm not hiding any bombs", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Taking over that place? Me? Hey, you need a rest fella. I'm not hiding any bombs", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Oh... You didn't? Hey, relax", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We're giving you just three years to clear your forces out of that place. After that, we're going to bomb all of that place", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "that place, that place, what's the difference", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Oh wait, that is the phone. Hello", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh.  Hey, it's my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Just shut up and listen. You've unleashed a monster onto that place and only you can get rid of him. Even though I hate you, and I wish you had cancer", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "YOU'RE a dick", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You are such a dick, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "YOU'RE a dick", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "YOU'RE a dick", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "YOU'RE a dick", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "YOU'RE a dick", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "YOU'RE a dick", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "...\", \"dependency_gramma", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "YOU'RE a dick", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Why is that", "docId": "South-Park-Terrance-&-Phillip-in-Not-Without-My-Anus.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yes, apparently he does", "qsentId": 40}]